[{"answer": "It's absolutely clear that he is a bigot and this isn't the case of him listing 11 sins and gay just happened to be on the list.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Marc Lamont Hill, this guy is just a bigot, Ben, isn't he?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "First, he did express things in a rather crude way but would you got very upset about quoting from his message in Pennsylvania.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "What is your view on this, sir?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "If you let me finish, I'll tell you how.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Are you sure about that?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Or just have a common sense.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "This guy needs to go much 12 years of slave, doesn't he, Marc Lamont Hill?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "ERGUSON: Today, I want to say that this is my problem with this.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "Which one?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "Wait a minute.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "... he gets booted off and then how can it possibly be?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Let me tell you -- let me finish.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Now, wait a minute, are you saying gay?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Give me one who had the right to marry three women.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "Why should you Dr. Michael Brown be entitled to more rights in America than somebody who's gay?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "You personally would like to have more rights than a ...", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Piers Morgan, should he have that right, sir?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Marriage is union of man and a woman.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "... in America?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "... benefits on that.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "That's not -- what's the question I asked you?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "No, of course not.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Yes or no?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Let me -- OK.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "So should two brothers deal out to marry?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "You're getting silly, Dr. Brown.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "There are cases in court about this?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "This is what happens...", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Why is that ridiculous?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "I'm not sure...", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Courageous?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "I'm not sure it's courageous.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Marc Lamont Hill?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "You know what, absolutely.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "So am I right to feel as intense as I feel?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "And let me ask you this Star.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "These are the kinds of shows that we're celebrating nowadays quite frankly and you're all surprised?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "I have to tell you, I said many times I've had two great mentors in my career.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Obviously what do you make to Barbara, what an extraordinary career she's had, isn't she?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "That means a male.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "What does that word mean to you?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "A black male?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Black -- any kind, Chinese could say Nigga, but nigger or nigger.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Black or white?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Because that's the racist word.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Right where we started.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Where have we ended up you think at the year after debating all of this?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "Yeah, exactly.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Can I just say something, Piers?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "Yeah, absolutely.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "This guy is an extraordinary man in many ways, isn't he?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "... to play the ukulele.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Yeah?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "That's the biggest muscle you've seen for a while.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "That's it?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "... but twice.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "Three?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "Twice.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "Three?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "Did you have one?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Literally at war with everyone?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "The funniest part about Snoop Dogg, Snoop Lion, Snoop anything he wants to call him so Snoop is Snoop.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "Away from the old Snoop to -- well from Dogg to Lion, what of you make of it?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "Hi.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "Because he's a (inaudible)", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "What's the answer?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "Because he's fabulous.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 734, "question": "Nischelle?", "qSentId": 733}, {"answer": "Don't do it.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 739, "question": "Can I go for bleep?", "qSentId": 738}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean, you know, she said the conversation is happening and the truth of the matter is the conversation sadly isn't even happening.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 837, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 836}, {"answer": "It's going to take people to have the courage and strength to stand up against a very powerful.", "docId": "131219pmt", "aSentId": 851, "question": "Now, what is going to change this?", "qSentId": 850}]